Guide to the Chard Powers Smith Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1901-1978; Series I; 21.27; (51 boxes)
  - General Correspondence, 1910-1978
    - Clark McCutcheon Bookseller & Publisher, 1966-1973 (Box 6, Folder 246-252)
    - Clark, Roger and Sarah, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - Clarke, F., 1928 June 29 (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - Clay, George R., Cindy and Katherine, 1966-1972, undated (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Cleaves, Clara, 1956 March 21 (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - Clemens, Cyril, 1933-1961 (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - Clemens, J. R., 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - Closser, Myla Jo, 1940 November 24 (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - Clough, Bertha, undated (Box 7, Folder 260)
    - Clough, Ruth Crary, undated (Box 7, Folder 261)
    - Code, Mr., 1946 October 23 (Box 7, Folder 262)
    - Coe, Lloyd, 1957 October 15 (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - Cohen, Rose, 1924, undated (Box 7, Folder 264-268)
    - Cohen, Sol, 1935 October 17 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - Cohn, Arthur, 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Coleman, Carroll, 1965 December 15 (Box 8, Folder 271)
    - Collamore, H. B., 1962-1965 (Box 8, Folder 272)
    - Collier Books, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 273)
    - Collins, Arthur, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 274)
    - Collins-Knowlton-Wing, Inc., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 275)
    - Collins, Mark, 1927 June 1 (Box 8, Folder 276)
    - Collins Publisher, 1954 July 28 (Box 8, Folder 277)
    - The Colorado Quarterly, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 278)
    - Colum, Mary and Padraic, 1948-1960 (Box 8, Folder 279)
    - Columbia Pictures Corporation, 1941 August 8 (Box 8, Folder 280)
    - Columbia University, 1949-1951 (Box 8, Folder 281)
    - Columbia University Press, 1948, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 282)
    - The Commonweal, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 283)
    - Compton, Ida, 1968 October 23 (Box 8, Folder 284)
    - Conant, Isabel Fiske, 1943 March 19 (Box 8, Folder 285)
    - Condé, Grace, undated (Box 8, Folder 286)
    - Conde, Katharine, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 287)
    - Congdon, Helen, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 288)
    - Congress of American Poets, 1936 July 22 (Box 8, Folder 289)
    - Conklin, Judy, 1944 December 26 (Box 8, Folder 290)
    - Conklin, Julia, 1945 July 18 (Box 8, Folder 291)
    - Connecticut. Attorney General, 1940 December 22 (Box 8, Folder 292)
    - Connecticut. Commissioner of Motor Vehicles, 1941 February 13 (Box 8, Folder 293)
    - Connecticut. Connecticut Public Library Committee, 1942 October (Box 8, Folder 294)
      I8ncludes: Wead, Katharine H.
    - Connecticut. Judicial Department, 1941 May (Box 8, Folder 295)
    - Connecticut. Supreme Court of Errors, undated (Box 8, Folder 296)
    - Connecticut. State of, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 297)
    - Connecticut. Secretary of State, 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 298)
    - Connecticut Chamber of Commerce, Inc., 1942 October (Box 8, Folder 299)
    - Connecticut College for Women, 1949 July 28 (Box 8, Folder 300)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association, undated (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - Connecticut Historical Society, 1948-1953 (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - Connecticut Light & Power Co., 1942-1948 (Box 8, Folder 303)
    - Connecticut State Library, 1945 November 21 (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - Connor, Michael A., 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - Conroy, Emma D., 1967-1974 (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - Contemporary Arts, undated (Box 8, Folder 307)
    - Contemporary Authors, 1966 November 9 (Box 8, Folder 308)
    - Contemporary Verse, 1926, undated (Box 8, Folder 309)
    - Cook, Julia A., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 310)
    - Cook, Reginald L., 1967-1972 (Box 8, Folder 311)
    - Copland, Aaron, 1961-1973 (Box 8, Folder 312)
    - Cornwall (Conn.: Town), 1939-1955 (Box 8, Folder 313)
    - Countryman Press, 1937 September 30 (Box 8, Folder 314)
    - Cousins, Norman, 1966-1971 (Box 8, Folder 315)
      See also: Saturday Review
    - Covington, Deborah, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 316)
    - Coward-McCann, Inc., 1937-1973 (Box 8, Folder 317)
    - Cowley, Malcolm, 1931-1976 (Box 8, Folder 318)
    - Cox, Lee Sheriden, 1974 June 12 (Box 8, Folder 319)
    - Crain, Maurice, 1935, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 320)
    - Cook, Ruth, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 321)
    - Crosby, Katherine N., 1948 December 4 (Box 8, Folder 322)
    - Crosby, Robert S., undated (Box 8, Folder 323)
    - Crossman, Edgar, 1937-1947 (Box 8, Folder 324-325)
    - Crossthwaite, Alexie, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 326)
    - Cummings, ----, 1950 March 18 (Box 8, Folder 327)
    - Cummings, Tony, 1971 February 5 (Box 8, Folder 328)
    - Curtis Brown, Ltd., 1936-1940 (Box 8, Folder 329)
    - Curtis, Philip, 1939 August 14 (Box 8, Folder 330)
    - The Cyrenius H. Booth Library, Newtown, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 331)
    - Czarnecki, Marguerite, 1961 August 6 (Box 8, Folder 332)
    - "D" General, 1911-1967 (Box 9, Folder 333)
    - Dalton Free Public Library, 1942-1946 (Box 9, Folder 334)
    - Daly, Jim, 1924-1941 (Box 9, Folder 335)
    - Damon, Bertha, undated (Box 9, Folder 336)
    - Damon, S. Foster, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 337)
    - Danbury Library, 1942 November 5 (Box 9, Folder 338)
    - Danbury State Teachers College, 1943-1946 (Box 9, Folder 339)
    - Dane, Paul and Evelyn, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 340)
    - Daniels, John Jr., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 341)
    - Daniels, Mabel, 1946, undated (Box 9, Folder 342)
    - Dashiell, Camelia, 1940 May 7 (Box 9, Folder 343)
    - David M. Hunt Library, Falls Village, 1944 February 6 (Box 9, Folder 344)
    - David, Mabel, 1935 December 2 (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - Davids, Corinne, 1968 Aubust 20 (Box 9, Folder 346)
    - Davidson, Donald, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 347)
    - Davidson, Gustav, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 348)
    - Davidson, Sidney W., 1940 February 23 (Box 9, Folder 349)
    - Davis, Paul and Helen, 1965 October 26 (Box 9, Folder 350)
    - Davis Polk Wardwell Gardiner & Reed, 1935 October 5 (Box 9, Folder 351)
    - Davis, Dr. Robert, 1971 May 6 (Box 9, Folder 352)
    - Davison, Edward, 1926-1927 (Box 9, Folder 353)
    - Davison, F. Trubee, 1965 April 6 (Box 9, Folder 354)
    - Dawson family, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 355)
    - Dawson, Peg, 1950-1957, undated (Box 9, Folder 356)
    - Day, Emma S., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 357)
    - Decker, ----, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 358)
    - Decker, Mary Bell, 1952 March 10 (Box 9, Folder 359)
    - Defenders of 3 Against HUAC, 1965 November 8 (Box 9, Folder 360)
    - Dell Books, 1959 January 24 (Box 9, Folder 361)
    - DePillis, Marie S., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 362)
    - Derby Public Library, 1942 November 21 (Box 9, Folder 363)
    - Derrickson, Winifred, 1974 September 10 (Box 9, Folder 364)
    - DeValcourt, ----, 1954 February 22 (Box 9, Folder 365)
    - Devane, ----, 1949 August 23 (Box 9, Folder 366)
    - DeVoti, William, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 367)
    - Dial Press, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 368)
    - Dickey, James, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 369)
    - Dickinson, Sidney, 1960 November 21 (Box 9, Folder 370)
    - Diggs, Debby, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 371)
    - Diggs, Peggy, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 372)
    - Dillon, George, 1935-1936 (Box 9, Folder 373)
    - Dillon, Mary B., 1948 August 10 (Box 9, Folder 374)
    - Distributist-Agrarian Movement, 1936-1945
      - General, 1933-1937 (Box 9, Folder 375-378)
      - The American Review, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 379)
      - Borsodi, Ralph, 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 380-381)
      - Burt, Struthers, 1936 May 7 (Box 10, Folder 382)
      - Committee for the Alliance of Agrarian and Distributist Groups, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 383)
      - The Commonweal, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 384)
      - The Cooperative League, 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 385)
      - Fisher, Willis, 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 386)
      - Free America, 1936-1945 (Box 10, Folder 387-388)
      - Ransom, John Crowe, 1936 May 27 (Box 10, Folder 389)
      - Tate, Allen, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 390)
    - Dobbs, Harvey T., 1938 (Box 10, Folder 391)
    - Dodd, Mead & Company, 1941 January 2 (Box 10, Folder 392)
    - Dole, Gertrude E., 1965 April 12 (Box 10, Folder 393)
    - Donaldson, Norman, 1959 November 25 (Box 10, Folder 394)
    - Donaldson, Scott, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 395)
    - Donovan, Hope and Robert, 1964-1967 (Box 10, Folder 396)
    - The Double Dealer, 1925 July 7 (Box 10, Folder 397)
    - Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1955-1963 (Box 10, Folder 398)
    - Douglas, Edward, 1910 January 14 (Box 10, Folder 399)
    - Douglas Library, Canaan, CT, 1942-1945 (Box 10, Folder 400)
      Includes: Smith, May Calista
    - Dover Publications, Inc., 1964-1972 (Box 10, Folder 401)
    - Dowling, Peg, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 402)
    - Downey, F., 1940 (Box 10, Folder 403)
    - Draper, J. H., 1936 November 12 (Box 10, Folder 404)
    - Dreifuss, Aurthur, 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 405)
    - Dublin Castle. Genealogical Office, 1954 December 2 (Box 10, Folder 406)
    - Dubois, Rachel, 1967 August 20 (Box 10, Folder 407)
    - Duncan, Alex, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 408)
    - Durant, Kenneth, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 409)
    - Dusckas, Liberty, 1941 September 30 (Box 10, Folder 410)
    - Dutcher, Madeleine, 1942 November 23 (Box 10, Folder 411)
    - "E" General, 1962-1965 (Box 10, Folder 412)
    - E.P. Dutton & Co., Inc., 1947 October 30 (Box 10, Folder 413)
    - Eaton, Clement, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 414)
    - Edgar, Alwyn, 1927 October 13 (Box 10, Folder 415)
    - The Edward MacDowell Association, Inc., 1929-1965
    - Edmund B. Thompson Printer Hawthorn House, 1935 October 22 (Box 10, Folder 416)
    - Edwin Valentine Mitchell, Inc., 1934 February 24 (Box 10, Folder 417)
    - Erich, Lea, 1954-1972 (Box 10, Folder 418-420)
    - Eichenbery, Fritz, 1948 February 18 (Box 10, Folder 421)
    - Eislestone, Eric, 1929 (Box 10, Folder 422)
    - Elder, Robert A. Jr., 1940 November 5 (Box 11, Folder 423)
    - Eldredge, Evelyn, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 424)
    - Eldridge, Louis and Ruth, 1973 December (Box 11, Folder 425)
    - Elizabethan Club (Yale University), 1931 (Box 11, Folder 426)
    - Ellerton, Alice, 1928 December 6 (Box 11, Folder 427)
    - Ellis, John Gillett, undated (Box 11, Folder 428)
    - Embury, Lucy, 1942 August 6 (Box 11, Folder 429)
    - Emlen, Beth, 1965 September 14 (Box 11, Folder 430)
    - Emmanuel College, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 431)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 432)
    - Engel, Lewis G., 1951 October 27 (Box 11, Folder 433)
    - English, ----, 1953 November 8 (Box 11, Folder 434)
    - Epstein, Sigmund, 1948 July 18 (Box 11, Folder 435)
    - Ergaz, Doussia, 1958 June 24 (Box 11, Folder 436)
    - Ernst, Eric, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 437)
    - Erskine, John, 1924-1928 (Box 11, Folder 438)
    - Erving, Kit, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 439)
    - Esquire Magazine, undated (Box 11, Folder 440)
    - Eudy, Mary Cummings, 1935 November 2 (Box 11, Folder 441)
    - Evan, Geraldine, 1926 January 1 (Box 11, Folder 442)
    - Evans, Arthur, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 443)
    - Evans, Nichols, 1965 December (Box 11, Folder 444)
    - Evanti, Lillian, 1959 August 10 (Box 11, Folder 445)
    - Evolution: A Journal of Nature, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 446)
    - "F" General, 1940-1959 (Box 11, Folder 447)
    - F---, Katharine, 1911, undated (Box 11, Folder 448)
    - Fair, Charles, 1963-1973 (Box 11, Folder 449)
    - Fain, Kitty, 1966-1975 (Box 11, Folder 450)
    - Farma, William J., 1934 December 17 (Box 11, Folder 451)
    - Farrar & Rinehart, Inc., 1940-1946 (Box 11, Folder 452)
      See also: Allen, Hervey
      See also:Farrar, John
    - Farrar, John, 1935-1946 (Box 11, Folder 453)
    - Farrar, Straus & Giroux, Inc., 1961-1977 (Box 11, Folder 454)
    - Faulder, Ann, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 455)
    - Fawcett Publications, 1971 August 16 (Box 11, Folder 456)
    - Fell, Elizabeth H., 1928 (Box 11, Folder 457)
    - Fenner, Phyllis, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 458)
    - Fenton, Charles, 1955 June 9 (Box 11, Folder 459)
    - Fessenden, Ken, 1925-1942 (Box 11, Folder 460)
    - Field, Jonathan and Gus, 1974, undated (Box 11, Folder 461)
    - Fields, Rachel, 1929-1935 (Box 11, Folder 462)
    - Fillmore, Parker, 1925-1939 (Box 11, Folder 463)
    - Finch Junior College, 1948 May 6 (Box 11, Folder 464)
    - Fineman, Irving and Esther, 1932-1974 (Box 11, Folder 465-468)
    - First National Bank, North Bennington, 1961-1965, undated (Box 12, Folder 469)
    - Fisher, Jack, 1950-1972 (Box 12, Folder 470)
      See also: Harper's Magazine
    - Fisher, Willis, 1937-1938, undated (Box 12, Folder 471)
    - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 472)
    - Fisher, Irving, 1936 January 17 (Box 12, Folder 473)
    - Fitzgibbon, C. K., 1935-1941, undated (Box 12, Folder 474)
    - Flack, Vic, 1966, undated (Box 12, Folder 475)
    - Flanner, Hildegard, 1968 January 2 (Box 12, Folder 476)
    - Fleischer, Charles and Mabel, 1935-1939 (Box 12, Folder 477)
    - Flexner, Beatrice, undated (Box 12, Folder 478)
    - Fletcher, Robert and Virginia, 1941-1953 (Box 12, Folder 479)
    - Flint, Richard Foster, 1942 December 28 (Box 12, Folder 480)
    - Foote, Caroline C., undated (Box 12, Folder 481)
    - Forrest, Elaine, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 482)
    - Fortiss, Karl E., 1944 (Box 12, Folder 483)
    - Fosdick, Harry E., 1936 (Box 12, Folder 484)
    - Foss, Lukas, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 485)
    - Foster, Kenneth B., 1973 December 11 (Box 12, Folder 486)
    - Fouiri, Emil and Mary, 1943 March 5 (Box 12, Folder 487)
    - Fowler, Bertram, 1937 June 29 (Box 12, Folder 488)
    - Fowler, Dorothy, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 489)
    - Fox Chase Agency, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 490-491)
    - Fox, Karleen, 1910-1911 (Box 12, Folder 492)
    - Franchere, Hoyt C., 1963-1965 (Box 12, Folder 493)
    - The Frank H. Gibson Press, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 494)
    - Fransioli, Betty, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 495)
    - Fraser, Rodney, 1955-1965 (Box 12, Folder 496)
    - Frederick, Claude, 1960 November 21 (Box 12, Folder 497)
    - Freed, Isadore, 1947 November 20 (Box 12, Folder 498)
    - Freeman, D. S., 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 499)
    - Freiday, Dean, 1968 September 12 (Box 12, Folder 500)
    - Friends Seminary Correspondence, 1952-1974, undated
      - A-G, 1956-1974, undated (Box 12, Folder 501-510)
      - H-Y, 1952-1973, undated (Box 13, Folder 511-535)
    - French, ----, 1945 July 14 (Box 14, Folder 536)
    - Freundlich, Irwin, 1963, undated (Box 14, Folder 537)
    - Frost, Betty, 1927-1929 (Box 14, Folder 538)
    - Frost, Frances, 1932-1933, undated (Box 14, Folder 539)
    - Frothingham, Bertha S., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 540)
    - Fullbright, J. W. (Senator), 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 541)
    - Furniss, ----, 1949 August 23 (Box 14, Folder 542)
    - Fussell, Edwin, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 543)
    - "G" General, 1927-1967 (Box 14, Folder 544)
    - Gabriel, Ralph, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 545)
    - Gallant, Cliff, 1965 May 15 (Box 14, Folder 546)
    - Gallatin, Edith, 1942 January 15 (Box 14, Folder 547)
    - Gallup, Donald C., 1957-1976 (Box 14, Folder 548-550)
    - Ganger, Ray, undated (Box 14, Folder 551)
    - Gangi, Adelaide, 1946 August 20 (Box 14, Folder 552)
    - Gannett, Lewis and Ruth, 1944-1964 (Box 14, Folder 553)
    - Gardiner (Me.), undated (Box 14, Folder 554)
    - Garrieau, Ed, undated (Box 14, Folder 555)
    - Garrigue, Jean, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 556)
    - Garrity, W. Arthur (Judge), 1968 January 5 (Box 14, Folder 557)
    - Gates, Larry, 1959 June 27 (Box 14, Folder 558)
    - Gavin, Richard, 1955-1958 (Box 14, Folder 559)
    - Geary, Don, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 560)
    - George, R. S., 1941 March 24 (Box 14, Folder 561)
    - Georges Borchard, Literary Agent, 1958 May 14 (Box 14, Folder 562)
    - Gessel, Edwin H., undated (Box 14, Folder 563)
    - Gidlow, Elsa, 1934-1940 (Box 14, Folder 564)
    - Gilarr, Agnes, undated (Box 14, Folder 565)
    - Gilbert, Alice, 1971 July 20 (Box 14, Folder 566)
    - Gilchrist, Marie E., 1929-1974 (Box 14, Folder 567-568)
    - Giles, Fuller & Goodwin, 1947 January 24 (Box 14, Folder 569)
    - Glenn, Frank, 1939 October 6 (Box 14, Folder 570)
    - Glover, Milton H., 1942-1943 (Box 15, Folder 571)
    - Glynn, Anthony and Susan, 1963-1973, undated (Box 15, Folder 572-573)
    - Glynn, Caroline, 1951-1963 (Box 15, Folder 574)
    - Glynn, Victoria, undated (Box 15, Folder 575)
    - Goddard College. The Eliot Prat Center, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 576)
    - Goldbeck, Eva, 1928-1935 (Box 15, Folder 577)
    - The Golden Quills Press, 1958-1973 (Box 15, Folder 578)
    - Goldstone, Alice Lewis, 1931 July 23 (Box 15, Folder 579)
    - Goodwin, Francis, 1951 February 12 (Box 15, Folder 580)
    - Goodwin, Henry, undated (Box 15, Folder 581)
    - Goodwin, Irving H., undated (Box 15, Folder 582)
    - Goodwin, Sue and Sage, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 583)
    - Goodyear, A. Conger, 1935-1936 (Box 15, Folder 584)
    - Gordon, Ruth, 1972 November 15 (Box 15, Folder 585)
    - Goshen, CT. Town Clerk, 1945 May 12 (Box 15, Folder 586)
    - Gotham, Robert M., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 587)
    - Governeur, Carol, undated (Box 15, Folder 588)
    - Graham, Mrs. Donald L., undated (Box 15, Folder 589)
    - Graham, Margaret, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 590)
    - Graham, Thomas, 1935 November 22 (Box 15, Folder 591)
    - Gray, Bernard A., 1935-1960 (Box 15, Folder 592)
    - Gray, David M., 1949 January 24 (Box 15, Folder 593)
    - Green, Mary Ann, undated (Box 15, Folder 594)
    - Greenberg Publisher, 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 595)
    - Greene, Dick, 1967-1971 (Box 15, Folder 596)
    - Greenleaf, William and Ellen, 1949-1961 (Box 15, Folder 597)
    - Greenslet, Ferris, 1935-1936 (Box 15, Folder 598)
    - Greenwod, Jane B., 1956 April 27 (Box 15, Folder 599)
    - Gregor, David G., 1935 October 5 (Box 15, Folder 600)
    - Gregory, Horace, 1931-1950 (Box 15, Folder 601)
    - Gregory, Marya, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 602)
    - Gregory, William K, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 603)
    - Griffiths, Bede, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 604)
    - Grimes, William and Janet, 1963-1969 (Box 15, Folder 605)
    - The Grosvenor Library, 1940 January 11 (Box 15, Folder 606)
    - Grove Press, Inc., 1959 (Box 15, Folder 607)
    - Grumman, Louise, 1960 January 2 (Box 15, Folder 608)
    - Guggenheim Foundation, 1948-1959 (Box 16, Folder 609)
    - Guglieni, O. Louis, 1935, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 610)
    - Guion, H. G., 1959 (Box 16, Folder 611)
    - Gunn Memorial Library, 1942-1946 (Box 16, Folder 612)
    - "H" General, 1940-4963 (Box 16, Folder 613)
    - H.W. Wilson Company, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 614)
    - Haas, Grace, 1911 (Box 16, Folder 615)
    - Haas, Ivan, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 616)
    - Haas, Merle, 1964 July 26 (Box 16, Folder 617)
    - Habgood, Thomas E., 1935 October 8 (Box 16, Folder 618)
    - Hackett, Hannah, 1967 February 10 (Box 16, Folder 619)
    - Hackett, Mildred, 1925 November 18 (Box 16, Folder 620)
    - Hackett, Thomas and Jeanette, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 621)
    - Hadley, Morris, 1935-1967 (Box 16, Folder 622)
    - Hagedorn, Hermann, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 623)
    - Haigh, Andrew, 1943 March 2 (Box 16, Folder 624)
    - Haldane, Sean, 1968-1968 (Box 16, Folder 625)
    - Hale, Sanderson, Byrnes & Morton, 1944 August 3 (Box 16, Folder 626)
    - Hale, Thomas Shaw, 1961-1965 (Box 16, Folder 627)
    - Halff, A., 1937 March 17 (Box 16, Folder 628)
    - Hallett, James, 1941 May 24 (Box 16, Folder 629)
    - Hamilton, Archer B., 1941 February 3 (Box 16, Folder 630)
    - Hamilton College, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 631)
    - Hamilton, David, 1924-1928 (Box 16, Folder 632)
    - Handlin, Oscar, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 633)
    - Handy, H. B., 1931-1932 (Box 16, Folder 634)
    - Hanks, June, 1965-1973, undated (Box 16, Folder 635)
    - Hannaway, C. P., 1926 July 22 (Box 16, Folder 636)
    - Hansen, Harry, 1936 January 17 (Box 16, Folder 637)
    - Hansen, Polly, undated (Box 16, Folder 638)
    - Hanson, Pierre, 1937 November 10 (Box 16, Folder 639)
    - Harcourt, Brace & Company, Inc., 1927-1958 (Box 16, Folder 640)
    - Harcourt, Brace & World, Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 16, Folder 641)
    - Harding, Cheryl, undated (Box 16, Folder 642)
    - Hardman, J. B. S., 1946 November 28 (Box 16, Folder 643)
    - Hare, Constance, 1928-1970 (Box 16, Folder 644)
    - Hare, Montgomery, 1967-1973, undated (Box 16, Folder 645)
    - Harrison, Polly, undated (Box 16, Folder 646)
    - Harkrider, John, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 647)
    - Harold Ober Associates, 1946-1958, undated (Box 16, Folder 648)
    - Harper & Brothers, 1926-1960 (Box 16, Folder 649)
    - Harper and Row, 1963-1972 (Box 16, Folder 650)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1937-1965 (Box 16, Folder 651)
    - Harrington, Helen, 1960, undated (Box 16, Folder 652)
    - Harris, Arthur, undated (Box 16, Folder 653)
    - Harris, F. Mai, 1911 October 31 (Box 16, Folder 654)
    - Harris, John B., 1935 December 11 (Box 16, Folder 655)
    - Harris, Roger, 1960 September 12 (Box 16, Folder 656)
    - Harrison, Edward, 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 657)
    - Harry N. Abrams, Inc., 1963 April 12 (Box 16, Folder 658)
    - Harsen, Felix, 1933 December 7 (Box 17, Folder 659)
    - Harson, Pierre, 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 660)
    - Hart, A. E., 1961-1972 (Box 17, Folder 661)
    - Harte, Charles Rufus, 1942-1945 (Box 17, Folder 662)
    - Hartford, H., 1959 February 10 (Box 17, Folder 663)
    - Hartford National Bank and Trust Co., 1935-1965 (Box 17, Folder 664-665)
    - Hartley, Wesley, 1959 September 6 (Box 17, Folder 666)
    - Hartman, Ralph D., 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 667)
    - Harvard University, 1928, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 668)
    - Harvard University Library, 1961 October 1 (Box 17, Folder 669)
    - Harvard University Press, 1955-1964 (Box 17, Folder 670)
    - Harvey, Eric, 1959 February 7 (Box 17, Folder 671)
    - Harwood, Michael, 1967-1973 (Box 17, Folder 672)
    - Harwood, Reed, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 673)
    - Hastings House Publishers, 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 674)
    - Hawley, Hudson, 1943 August 30 (Box 17, Folder 675)
    - Hayashi, Kenichiro, 1971 February 1 (Box 17, Folder 676)
    - Hayes, Gertrude, 1947 October 10 (Box 17, Folder 677)
    - Hayloft Book & Print Shop, 1948 October 19 (Box 17, Folder 678)
    - Hays, May B., 1946 October 19 (Box 17, Folder 679)
    - Headley, Hubert Klyne, 1940-1954 (Box 17, Folder 680)
    - Hemingway, Ernest, 1927-1950, undated (Box 17, Folder 681)
    - The Hemlock Press, 1971-1974 (Box 17, Folder 682)
    - Henry Holt & Co., Inc., 1959 December 2 (Box 17, Folder 683)
    - Herald, L. Srabian, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 684)
    - Hermitage House, Inc., 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 685-686)
    - Herrick, E. S., 1936-1956 (Box 17, Folder 687)
    - Hewes, Phillip and Mary, 1936-1975 (Box 17, Folder 688)
    - Hewes, Thomas, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 689)
    - Heyward, DuBose and Dorothy, 1925-1965, undated (Box 17, Folder 690)
    - Hibbell, Paxlau and Sheila, undated (Box 17, Folder 691)
    - Hickok, James L., 1943 (Box 17, Folder 692)
    - Hicks, Granville and Dorothy, 1960-1974 (Box 17, Folder 693-694)
    - Hier, Ethel Glenn, 1940-1946 (Box 17, Folder 695)
    - Hildreth, Florence, 1950 July 31 (Box 17, Folder 696)
    - Hill and Wang, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 17, Folder 697)
    - Hill, Ralph Nading, 1959 November 8 (Box 17, Folder 698)
    - Hilliard, B., 1963 (Box 17, Folder 699)
    - Hillyer, Robert, 1933-1949 (Box 17, Folder 700)
    - Hirsch, Adalfine, 1927 April 8 (Box 17, Folder 701)
    - Hirsch, C., 1928 December 20 (Box 17, Folder 702)
    - Hjördis Swenson, Scandinavian Literary Center, 1939 October 11 (Box 17, Folder 703)
    - Hobson, S., 1926 January 11 (Box 17, Folder 704)
    - The Hodge Memorial Library, Roxbury, CT, 1942 November 17 (Box 17, Folder 705)
    - Hoffman, Elizabeth, 1928 February 27 (Box 17, Folder 706)
    - Hogg, Mary, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 707)
    - Holberg, Ruth, 1946 July 3 (Box 18, Folder 708)
    - Holden, Barbara and Raymond, 1963-1974 (Box 18, Folder 709)
    - Holden, Sarah H. H., 1950 November 1 (Box 18, Folder 710)